infoscoutinc.com 2017-09-09

# InfoScout | Privacy Policy

Effective Date: June 21st, 2013

ScoutIt, Inc. (InfoScout’s parent company) recognizes that you should have the right to know how the data we collect is used and what controls you have over that data once shared with us.

ScoutIt, Inc. is in the business of operating, administering, and providing Market Research and Rewards Programs to help consumers receive value back when they shop and to help brands and retailers better understand consumer behavior. This Privacy Policy applies to all information collected by ScoutIt, Inc., Inc. and any corporate affiliates (collectively, “ScoutIt, Inc.”) for current and former consumers in connection with all the products, services, websites and mobile applications we offer on behalf of ourselves or others. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully and contact us if you have any questions or concerns. 

## What information does ScoutIt, Inc. collect?

We may collect the following types of information: 

#### Information you provide

We receive and store the information you enter on ScoutIt, Inc. websites or mobile applications or you otherwise provide us in any other way, for example, where we are the service provider for a Rewards Program. Wherever we provide examples of information in this Privacy Policy, the examples are not intended to be an exhaustive list.

#### Information about your purchases with Participating Retailers

We may receive information about your purchases from Participating Retailers.

#### Award information

We will maintain records to keep track of the Awards you earn.

#### Information from cookies

When you visit a ScoutIt, Inc. website or click on a banner advertisement, we may send one or more cookies to your computer or other device. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some ScoutIt, Inc. website features or services may not function properly without cookies.

#### Log and other information

When you access a ScoutIt, Inc. website, email, advertisement, or other content served by or on behalf of us on other websites or mobile applications, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website. These server logs typically include your web request, Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser or Account(s) to us. Other actions, such as interactions with advertisements, may also be included in our server logs. During some visits to our websites we may use software tools such as JavaScript to measure and collect session information, including page response times, download errors, length of visits to certain pages, page interaction information (such as scrolling, clicks, and mouse-overs), and methods used to browse away from the page.

#### Information from other sources

We may receive information about you from various sources. This may include estimated demographic information from data collection companies and others in order for us to offer anonymous market research reports to clients and partners.

We may link Nonpersonal Information about you with any Personal Information we have.

## How does ScoutIt, Inc. use my information?

#### To manage your Account(s)

We use the information we collect to manage your Account(s). For example, we use the information you provide us and the purchase information we collect to track, process, post and fulfill Awards you earn and to provide customer service. In addition, we may use this information to keep you informed of new features and product developments as well as to provide more relevant offers to you.

#### To contact you

We may use the contact information we receive from you or third parties to contact you via email, direct mail, telephone or other channels such as text messaging, Facebook and Twitter, in each case provided we are permitted by law to send such communications to you and you have not otherwise opted-out of receiving them. For example, we may, on behalf of or at the request of, the Rewards Program Sponsor(s) for the Rewards Program(s) you participate in, use your contact information to send you emails about our products or services and/or the product and services of Rewards Program Sponsors, Award Providers, Participating Retailers, or others. We may also use your contact information to provide you administrative communications from time to time.

#### For market research purposes

We use the information we collect to provide clients with anonymous market research reports. For example, “What percentage of Females in the Midwest buy Brand X products?” We may also partner with third-party market research companies who may leverage the data to support the creation of their own anonymous market research reports based on proprietary data they collect via other sources. However, your data shall NOT be sold to third-parties for the purposes of marketing to you.

#### To develop, evaluate, improve and deliver our products and services

We use the information we collect to develop, evaluate, improve and deliver our product and services, and the products and services of Rewards Program Sponsors, Award Providers, Participating Retailers, or others. For example, if we learn from the information we collect that certain brands or categories of products are highly valuable to Registered Users, we may offer more services or Awards for those products. 

#### To deliver personalized advertisements and other information to you

We may use the information we collect to deliver advertisements about our products and services, and/or the products and services of Rewards Program Sponsors, Award Providers, Participating Retailers, or others on our websites, other websites, mobile applications, or in other marketing channels. For example, we may use the purchase information we collect about you because of your participation in one or more Rewards Program(s) to deliver to you, via one or more of those channels, advertisements that we, or the parties whose products or services we are promoting, think may be of interest to you. We also may engage third party advertising networks to deliver these advertisements. These networks use cookies and similar technologies to personalize the advertising content you see and to measure the effectiveness of the advertisements they deliver. These companies are authorized to use the information we provide and they collect when you navigate to a website within the ad network to provide this service to us.

#### Fulfill legal and regulatory requirements

We may use the information we collect to comply with federal, state, or other applicable laws and regulations.

#### Protect the rights or property of ScoutIt, Inc. or our Registered Users

We also may use the information we collect to the extent we believe it is necessary or appropriate to enforce or apply our rights under our agreements with Registered Users, and/or to protect the rights, property or safety of ScoutIt, Inc., our Registered Users and others.

## How does ScoutIt, Inc. share your information?

#### Personal Information

We may share Personal Information with Rewards Program Sponsors. In the future, we may also share information with partner companies that either are subject to this Privacy Policy or follow practices at least as protective as those described in this Privacy Policy with respect to the Personal Information we share with them.

#### Information we share with Rewards Program Sponsors

We work closely with our Rewards Program Sponsors. If you participate in a Rewards Program, we may provide the Rewards Program Sponsor for that Rewards Program any Personal Information we receive about you including, without limitation, your name, mailing address, email address, phone number, username, Account activity, including information about the Award offers you activated and redeemed. Rewards Program Sponsors are third party companies independent of ScoutIt, Inc. that may use the information we provide them to evaluate, develop, offer and promote their products and services to you and others.

#### Contests, sweepstakes and surveys

We may promote or offer contests, sweepstakes, similar promotional offers or surveys that may be co-sponsored by ScoutIt, Inc. and one or more other companies, or may be sponsored by companies other than ScoutIt, Inc.. Some or all of the Personal Information collected through these offers or surveys may be shared with the sponsor(s) or other companies indicated on the entry form, in the governing rules or on the survey, as applicable.

#### Agents and service providers

We engage other companies and individuals to perform certain services and functions on our behalf. For example, we may engage third parties to send email and postal mail, analyze data, provide marketing services, process applications, provide search results and links (including paid listings and links), and provide customer service. We contractually obligate these service providers to access and use the Personal Information we make available to them only as needed to perform their functions and for no other purposes.

#### Information we share with nonaffiliated third parties as permitted by law:

We reserve the right to disclose Personal Information to the extent permitted by applicable law, for example:

#### Business transfers:

If there is a change of control in ScoutIt, Inc.’s business (whether by merger, sale, or otherwise), your Personal Information could be included as part of that transaction and could be used by the purchaser. We will notify you by email if your Personal Information will become subject to a different privacy policy after the transaction.

#### Protection of ScoutIt, Inc. and others:

We may disclose Personal Information about you to third parties when we believe such disclosure is appropriate to comply with a legal requirement, such as a law, regulation, court order, subpoena or search warrant, or in the course of a legal proceeding. We may also disclose Personal Information as we believe appropriate to enforce or apply our rights under our agreements with Registered Users, to protect the rights, property or safety of ScoutIt, Inc., our Registered Users and others, including exchanging information for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

#### With your consent:

In addition to the above, we may share Personal Information about you with others to the extent you consent to such sharing.

#### Nonpersonal Information

We may provide Nonpersonal Information about you to clients, partners, Rewards Program Sponsors, Award Providers, Participating Retailers, or others for marketing, analysis and other purposes. For example, your purchase information may be aggregated with the purchase information of other Registered Users and analyzed to evaluate the effectiveness of certain award offers or advertisements, and the results of that analysis may be shared with Rewards Program Sponsors, Award Providers, Participating Retailers, or others.

#### Security of Your Personal Information

ScoutIt, Inc. is committed to earning and keeping your trust. We understand the need for your Personal Information to remain secure and private, and we have implemented security practices and procedures designed to safeguard your information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Only ScoutIt, Inc. employees and service providers who need to use it as part of their jobs are authorized to have access to your Personal Information.

Please remember that you also play a valuable part in data security. You should never share your Account password, if applicable, with anyone. If you feel your password has been compromised, you should change it immediately. After you have finished using our mobile applications or website(s), you should log out of your Account and exit your browser so that no unauthorized persons can use our website under your name or Account.

#### Online Forums

Please note that information you voluntarily include in bulletin boards, chat rooms and other online forums we may offer may be viewed and used by anyone with access to those forums. ScoutIt, Inc. is unable to control any use of such information

#### Facebook Connect

We may provide you the ability to log in to our websites using sign-in services such as Facebook Connect or an Open ID provider. These services will authenticate your identity and provide you the option to share certain Personal Information with us such as your name and email address to pre-populate our sign up form. Services like Facebook Connect give you the option to post information about your activities on our website(s) to your profile page to share with others within your network.

#### Collection of Information from Children

None of our products or services is intended for use or purchase by children. Accordingly, ScoutIt, Inc. does not knowingly collect, either online or offline, information from children under the age of 13. If you believe that we might have any information from a child under age 13, please contact us.

## Changes to this Privacy Policy

Please note that this Privacy Policy may change from time to time so please review it frequently. We will post any Privacy Policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice by means of a notice on the Rewards Program homepages or by email to the email address we have on file in your Account. Each version of this Privacy Policy will be identified at the top of the Privacy Policy by its effective date, and we will also keep prior versions of this Privacy Policy in an archive for your review.

## Key Terms

#### Account

An “Account” is an account you establish with ScoutIt, Inc. or a Rewards Program.

#### Awards

“Awards” are the discounts, cash rebates, other cash Awards, points, coins, miles and/or other awards that Award Providers offer you as a Registered User of a Rewards Program.

#### Award Providers

An “Award Provider” is a company or other entity that offers you an award if you make an eligible purchase of the entity’s products or services through one or more Rewards Programs. Award Providers can include ScoutIt, Inc., consumer packaged goods manufacturers, grocery stores, drug stores or other entities.

#### Nonpersonal Information

“Nonpersonal Information” is any information about you that is not Personal Information.

#### Participating Retailers

“Participating Retailers” are retailers and other entities that sell products and services for which Award Providers offer Awards. Participating Retailers agree to provide or make available to us certain purchase information so that we may track Awards. A Participating Retailer can also be an Award Provider and/or a Rewards Program Sponsor.

#### Personal Information

“Personal Information” is information that personally identifies you to the person or entity that is in possession of such information.

#### Registered User

A “Registered User” is an individual or entity that registers to participate in one or more Rewards Programs to earn Awards

#### Rewards Program

A “Rewards Program” is a Rewards Program ScoutIt, Inc. operates and administers on its own behalf or on behalf of other entities. A Rewards Program could be a stand-alone Rewards Program or it could be a part of a larger Rewards Program offered by an entity. For example, ScoutIt, Inc. could operate the grocery portion of a Rewards Program offered by an entity. In that example, the grocery portion of the Rewards Program would be the “Rewards Program” subject to this Privacy Policy.

#### Rewards Program Sponsor

A “Rewards Program Sponsor” is ScoutIt, Inc. or a company, organization or other entity on whose behalf ScoutIt, Inc. is operating or administrating a Rewards Program. A Rewards Program Sponsor may also be an Award Provider or Participating Retailer.

#### ScoutIt, Inc. Website or our website

A “ScoutIt, Inc. Website”, which may also be referred to as “our website”, is any website ScoutIt, Inc. hosts or otherwise operates on behalf of itself, Rewards Program Sponsors, and any other entities. 

## Information you provide

In connection with your participation in a Rewards Program, you may provide us, or the Rewards Program Sponsor for the Rewards Program, information such as your name, mailing address, email address, phone number, username, password, and your grocery or drugstore loyalty card numbers so that we may track your qualified purchases with Award Providers. You also provide us information when you navigate our websites, use our mobile applications, activate Award offers, open and/or respond to our emails, participate in a contest or questionnaire, or communicate with us by phone, e-mail, or otherwise.

## Cookies

A “cookie” is a small file containing a string of characters that is sent to your computer when you visit a website. When you visit the website again, the cookie allows that site to recognize your browser. Cookies may store user preferences and other information.

## Unsubscribe

To unsubscribe from all future email, click the unsubscribe link in the welcome email or any subsequent email from ScoutIt, Inc.. You may also email us at contactus@infoscoutinc.com or call us at 408-716-8281 or write to us at:

ScoutIt, Inc. (InfoScout)

322 Ritch St

San Francisco, CA 94107
